AMC台《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously on the AMC's The Walking Dead...
我们赶走了他们
We drove them out.
我们应该乘胜追击
We should go after them.
我们应该做个了断
We should finish it.
你们如何活着  如何死去
How you live... how you die--
不是我说了算
it isn't up to me.
大家投票决定
We vote.
他开枪打死了那个孩子
He gunned that kid down.
我逼不得已才那么做
I did what I had to do.
我们都被感染了
We're all infected.
如果我杀死你
If I was to kill you,
你就会变成这种东西
you'd come back as one of these things.
总督人呢
Where's the Governor?
他见人就开枪
He fired on everyone.
把大家都杀光了
Killed them all.
他们会耍花招的
They're gonna drew on us.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译: 冰蓝  33来了  Reginamoon  送小孩
翻译: 重案组李Sir  卫老哥  Eowyn  小饭
时间轴: 涛涛  加森  雪贵人  后期:  青衣  吉吉
校对:Lemony  冰蓝  送小孩  Requiem  总监:Lemony  送小孩
行尸走肉  第四季第一集
你没叫醒我
You didn't wake me up.
因为我知道你整晚没睡
'Cause I knew you were up all night
一直在用手电筒看漫画
reading comics with a flashlight.
维奥莉特怎么了
What's up with Violet?
卡尔  我告诉过你别给它们取名字
Carl, I told you not to name them.
它们不再是小猪了  而是食物
They're not piglets anymore. They're food.
我只是觉得  直到...
I just thought, you know, until...
好吧
Okay.
我不知道她怎么了
I don't know what's going on with her.
可能生病了  也可能没事
Could be sick, could be nothing.
早日康复  维奥莉特
Feel better, Violet.
走  我们去忙吧
Come on, let's get to it.
早上好  达里尔
Morning, Daryl.
好啊  S医生
What's up, Dr. S?
-早上好  达里尔  -早上好  达里尔
- Morning, Daryl. - Morning, Daryl.
好啊  达里尔
Hey, Daryl!
闻起来挺香的
Smells good.
记住啊  是我先喜欢你的
Just so you know, I liked you first.
打住
Stop.
瑞克也带了很多人回来
You know, Rick brought in a lot of them, too.
最近没有
Not recently.
庇护陌生人
Give the stranger sanctuary,
给他们吃的
keeping people fed,
你得学会宽容的生活
you're gonna have to learn to live with the love.
是啊
Right.
我带你去看样东西
I need you to see something.
帕特里克  你能来接手吗
Patrick, you want to take over?
好  女士
Yes, ma'am.
迪克森先生
Mr. Dixon,
我只想感谢你昨天带回了那头鹿
I just wanted to thank you for bringing that deer back yesterday.
我们真是大饱口福  先生
It was a real treat, sir.
如果能和你握手  我将倍感荣幸
And I'd be honored to shake your hand.
今天  不知道我们这边能否
About today, I don't know if we're gonna be able
分出人进城
to spare a lot of people for the run.
那个地方已经清空了  我们会继续推进
That place is good to go. We're gonna move on it.
是啊
Yeah.
问题是  一夜之间行尸暴增
The thing is, we had a pretty big buildup overnight.
三号塔那边更多
Dozens more towards tower three.
情况和上个月一样糟
It's getting as bad as last month.
它们不再分散了
They don't spread out anymore.
人越多  就会吸引越多的行尸
With more of us sitting here, we're drawing more of them out.
很多行尸
You get enough of those
趴在围栏边  然后越聚越多
damn fence-clingers, they start to herd up.
又来推围墙了
Pushing against the fences again.
还撑得住  但得尽快行动  不然坚持不久
It's manageable, but unless we get ahead of it, not for long.
要辛苦你了  宝贝儿
Sorry, Pookie.
喜欢那样吧
You like that?
我觉得你今天还是别去了
I don't think you should go today.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Yeah.
我们有防爆服
We have the suits.
但你不用去
Yeah, but you don't have to go.
你不应该去
You shouldn't.
你知道一切都会好的  对吧
You know everything's gonna work out, right?
对吧
Right?
对
Right.
但你得留下  行吗
But you're staying, okay?
好吧
Fine.
你好  美女
Hey, beautiful.
你也好
Hey yourself.
-去穿个围裙  -好
- You need an apron. - Yeah.
能和你谈谈吗
Listen, can we talk?
我打算今天跟他们出去
I was thinking of going on the run today.
行啊
Okay.
我不喜欢隔着围栏爆它们的头
I don't like killing them on the fence.
讨厌的很
I hate it.
而在外面  它们向着你走过来
I mean, when they're coming at you out there,
那是不同的
it's different.
你想都不用想
You don't even think about it.
当它们层层趴在围栏上时
When they're stacked up against the chain-link,
面对面  我...
you're just face-to-face. I...
我只是想做点别的来帮忙
I just wanted to do something different to help out.
可你总是自告奋勇来做这事
You always volunteered to do it.
那是因为你总是在做
That's because you were always doing it.
我想多点机会了解你
Just thought I could get to know you.
你做到了
You did.
在外面小心点
You be careful out there.
我正想找你
I was just gonna come find you.
找我什么事
What's up?
委员会把大家从煤炭小队撤回来
Well, the council pulled back everyone on the coal crew
准备组织外出
from going on the run.
他们现在缺人手
They're shorthanded right now.
我觉得应该加入他们
I figured I'd step up to help, go with 'em.
只是想在走之前见你一面
Just, you know, wanted to make sure that I saw you before.
好吧
Okay.
我只是... 你知道的
I just-- 'cause, you know,
出去很危险
it's dangerous going out there.
我知道
I know.
好吧  那不跟我道别吗
Okay, are you gonna say good-bye?
才不呢
Nope.
整的跟言情小说似的
It's like a damn romance novel.
我想跟你们一起去
I'd like to start pulling my weight around here.
鲍勃  这才过了一周
Bob, it's only been a week.
这一周我能吃上饭
That's a week worth of meals,
有个安身之处
a roof over my head.
让我也发光发热好继续待在这里
Let me earn my keep.
-达里尔找到你时  你孤身一人  -是的
- You were out on your own when Daryl found you. - That's right.
我想知道  你会团队作战吗
I just want to make sure you know how to play on a team.
如果很困难  我们也不会去
We ain't gonna do it unless it's easy.
他可是军医
You know he was a medic in the Army.
你还真是难搞定  你知道吗
You a hell of a tough sell. You know that?
好吧
Okay.
这些叶子都会长在背阳处
These leaves are gonna be in the shade,
因此长不出什么好果子
so we won't get any good fruit from it.
所以我们就把它从这里掐断
So we just pinch it off here.
根茎断了  但它们还能生长
Things break, but they can still grow.
这些小枝  它们会扎根
These little bristles, they'll take root
然后我们就会有棵全新的植物了
and we'll have a whole new plant.
走吧
Let's go.
见到你我们真开心
We're glad to see you.
见到你们我也很开心
Glad to see you, too.
有人中头彩了
Somebody hit the jackpot.
不可能吧
No way.
太棒了  谢谢
Awesome! Thank you.
你看完了轮我看
I get to read 'em when you're done.
我还找到了这个
And I found this.
你脸上一片狼藉
Your face is losing the war.
你要待一段时间吗
You gonna stay a little while?
就待一会儿
Just a little while.
看看谁回来了
Well, look who's back.
我没找到他
Didn't find him.
真高兴看到你安全归来
Glad to see you in one piece.
我寻思着要在梅肯附近找找
I'm thinking of looking over near Macon.
这值得一试
It's worth a shot.
七十里路满是行尸
70 miles of walkers.
你有可能碰上几个不太友好的
You might run into a few unneighborly types.
不是吗
Is it?
我去看看基地
I'm gonna go check out the Big Spot.
我之前说过的那个  就去看看
The one I was talking about, just seeing.
是啊  我得出去检查一下陷阱
Yeah, I got to go out and check the snares.
我可不想把我们抓到的东西白白让给行尸
I don't want to lose whatever we catch to the walkers.
我去吧
I'll go.
你刚到这呢
You just got here.
我会回来的
And I'll be back.
-你要去检查陷阱  -是的
- Going to check the snares? - I am.
你不能去  去做你的杂事
You're not. Do your chores.
看你的漫画  或者读几本书
Read comics. Maybe some books, too.
去找帕特里克玩
Hang out with Patrick.
也许去参加故事会
Maybe go to story time.
老爸  那是小孩干的事
Dad, that's for kids.
是呀
Yeah.
现在  刷刷她
Now brush her down.
留在这里没什么不对的  瑞克
Nothing wrong with staying close, Rick.
每个人都能理解
Everyone understands.
你为我们种了足够的庄稼
You're growing us enough food
近期内你不用再四处奔波了
so we won't need to do runs soon.
但我们得给你找一套好点的连体工服了
But we do have to find you a good pair of overalls.
你看上去得像点样
You need to look the part.
嘴角上叼一株小麦
A little piece of wheat out of the corner of your mouth.
再长个农夫大臀
Maybe a bigger ass.
听着  委员会里其余的人
Listen, the rest of the council--
达里尔  格伦  卡萝尔  萨沙
Daryl, Glenn, Carol, Sasha,
他们所有人
all of them--
他们都想要我和你谈谈
they wanted me to talk to you.
当你出去的时候
When you go out there,
你必须得带上你的枪
you got to take your gun.
别担心
Easy now.
只不过是去围栏外
It's just outside the fence.
我带着我的刀呢
I have my knife.
我遇到麻烦的话  六发子弹也没什么用
I get in trouble, six bullets isn't gonna make the difference.
瑞克  我们不想让你出事
Rick, we want you to be safe.
带着你的枪
Bring your gun.
等等
Wait.
求你了
Please.
求你
Please?
求你帮帮我
Please help me.
我知道你不认识我
I know you don't know me.
好吗  我知道
Okay, I know that.
但是你能帮我把这个带给我丈夫吗
But can you please help me get this to my husband?
我们已经好几天没吃饭了
We haven't eaten in days.
给你  拿着
Here. Go ahead.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在这附近有营地吗
Do you have a camp around here?
有
Yeah.
我们能不能跟你回去
Could we possibly come back with you?
我们自己
We've been doing...
很难熬
very badly on our own.
我得见见他
I'd have to meet him.
我要问他几个问题  问你们俩
I need to ask him some questions, both of you.
什么问题
What questions?
就问三个
Just three.
我们到了再说
When we get there.
你身上有枪吗
You have a gun on you?
我能确认一下吗
Can I make sure?
好
Yeah.
我不认识你
Look, I don't know you,
所以我警告你
so I'm just gonna tell you this.
你要是跟我耍花招
You try anything--
任何花招
anything--
输的人会是你
you're gonna be the one who loses.
我已经一无所有了
I don't have anything else to lose.
不
No.
你有
You do.
拿着
Go ahead.
尼克  看这边
Nick, look over here.
这是维恩
This one's Wayne.
-尼克  -尼克  看这边
- Nick. - Nick, over here.
嗨  尼克
Hi, Nick!
-嗨  尼克  -你们给它们起名字了
- Hi, Nick. - You're naming them?
有一个行尸有名牌
Well, one of them has a name tag,
我们就觉得它们都应该有名字
so we thought all of them should.
它们活着的时候有名字  它们已经死了
They had names when they were alive. They're dead now.
不  它们没死  只是不一样了
No, they're not. They're just different.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
它们不能说话
Okay, they don't talk.
不能思考  它们吃人
They don't think. They eat people.
它们杀人
They kill people.
普通人也杀人  但他们还是有名字
People kill people. They still have names.
你们见过发生的事吗
Have you seen what happens?
你们见过有人那样死去的情景吗
Have you seen someone die like that?
是的  见过
Yeah, I have.
它们不是人  也不是宠物
They're not people and they're not pets.
别给它们起名字
Don't name them.
我们应该去看书  走吧
We're supposed to go read. Come on.
你今晚参加故事会吗
You coming to story time tonight?
好
Uh, yeah.
到时见
See you then.
我有时参加  我很幼稚
I go sometimes. I'm immature.
你不会喜欢的  是小孩的游戏
You wouldn't dig it. It's for kids.
我也走了
I'm gonna head up there, too.
一会儿再聊  小长官
I'll catch you later, young sir.
好
Yep.
军队来后竖起了这些围栏
Army came in and put these fences up.
建了一个避难基地
Made it a place for the people to go.
上周我们发现这个地方的时候
Last week when we spotted this place,
铁丝网后面有很多行尸
there was a bunch of walkers behind this chain-link
就像看门狗一样不让人进去
keeping people out like a bunch of guard dogs.
它们都离开了吗
So they all just left?
你听
Give a listen.
你把它们引走了
You drew 'em out.
三天前放了一个录音机在那儿
Put a boom box out there three days ago.
接在两块车用蓄电池上
Hooked it up to two car batteries.
好吧  我们来扫荡吧
All right, let's make a sweep.
注意安全  尽量多拿
Make sure it's safe. Grab what you can.
明天我们带更多的人过来
We'll come back tomorrow with more people.
来吧
Come on.
等一下
Just give it a second.
好吧  我觉得我明白了
Okay, I think I got it.
明白什么
Got what?
我一直想知道达里尔以前是干什么的
I've been trying to guess what Daryl did before the turn.
他已经瞎猜了差不多六个星期了
He's been trying to guess for, like, six weeks.
我在慢慢猜
Yeah, I'm pacing myself.
每天试一次
One shot a day.
好吧  说说看
All right, shoot.
你在监狱里的行为方式
Well, the way you are at the prison,
你是委员会成员  你会追踪
you being on the council, you're able to track,
你帮助人们  但是你还是有点
you're helping people, but you're still being kind of...
阴沉
surly.
然后我就懂了
Big swing here.
你是凶案警察
Homicide cop.
有什么好笑的
What's so funny?
没什么  相当说得通
Nothing. It makes perfect sense.
其实这家伙说的没错
Actually, the man's right.
我是卧底警察
Undercover.
-不会吧  真的吗  -真的
- Come on, really? - Yep.
我不喜欢谈论这个
I don't like to talk about it
因为真的挺操蛋的  你懂吗
'cause it was a lot of heavy shit, you know?
伙计  可别骗我  真的吗
Dude, come on, really?
好吧  看来我得接着猜了
Okay. I'll just keep guessing, I guess.
没错  接着猜吧
Yeah, you keep doing that.
-我们要开始吗  探长  -干吧
- We're gonna do this, Detective? - Let's do it.
好吧  我们进去  扫荡时保持队形
All right, we go in, stay in formation for the sweep.
你们都知道该找什么
After that, you all know what you're supposed to look for.
还有问题吗
Any questions?
我有没有没被你使唤过
Was there ever a time that you weren't the boss of me?
我出生之前有那么几年吧
You had a few years before I was born.
我们当时准备去巴亚尔塔港度蜜月
We were going to Puerto Vallarta for our honeymoon.
他们关闭了机场
When they shut down the airports,
我们的转接航班再也没出现
our connecting flight never connected.
我们不许离开航站楼  所以
They wouldn't let us leave the terminal, so...
我们就睡在
we slept next to these huge
来自津巴布韦的巨型大理石雕塑边
marble sculptures from Zimbabwe.
第四天夜里
Then, on the fourth night,
那些东西就进来了
the things just came through.
一开始我们有很多人
There were a lot of us and...
但现在只剩下埃迪和我了
now it's just Eddie and me.
如果不是因为他
And I wouldn't have made it
我根本挺不过来
if it wasn't for him.
如果不是因为
And it isn't that...
他一次又一次地救了我
he saved me over and over again
或者让我明白
or that he showed me the things
有些事不得不做  或者
that I had to do or...
应该主动去做
to be willing to do.
要不是因为他还在这里
If he wasn't still here...
我  我也早就完了
I-- I couldn't be.
我就是  我做不到
I just-- I couldn't.
你指什么事
What were they?
什么
What?
那些你不得不主动去做的事
The things you had to be willing to do?
吃我们能找到的任何食物
Eeating whatever we could find--
动物尸体
animal carcasses
腐烂的水果  还有
and rotten fruit-- and...
抛弃其他人
leaving people behind.
躲开那些需要援助的人
Hiding from people who needed my help.
你就不一样
Unlike you.
我也不是做慈善的
This is not charity.
人必须集体行动
You have to have numbers.
人是对抗行尸的最好武器
People are the best defense against walkers
或者对抗其他人
or people.
我们互相帮助
We help each other.
你管它们叫"行尸"
You call them "Walkers"?
你还好吧  有受伤吗
You all right? You cut or something?
没有  但我的脚被压住了
No, man, but my foot is caught.
好的  他被压住了  来帮我一把
All right. He's just caught. Come on, help me up.
-出什么事了  -大家都没事
- What happened? - Everyone's all right.
只是被红酒和啤酒淹没了
We're over in wine and beer.
我动作可快了  伙计  直接冲向酒瓶
I was moving fast, man. I drove right into the drinks.
伙计  是你运气好
Man, you lucked out.
这东西要是再偏一点...
If this thing had come down on you the wrong way...
我们该走了
Yeah, uh, we should probably go now.
鲍勃还被压着  把他弄出来
Bob's still stuck. Get him out of there.
我们去找其他人
We'll get the others.
我曾在机场看过那些雕塑
I saw those sculptures at the airport once.
我最喜欢孩子玩跳背游戏的那尊
My favorite was the kids playing leapfrog.
我也是
Mine, too.
埃迪和我不得不做的那些事
What Eddie and I had to do,
你也做过吗
did you do things like that?
做过吗
Did you?
你觉得做过那些事后  还能回到过去吗
Do you think you get to come back from them?
我希望如此
I hope so.
是吗
Yeah?
希望我们对你三个问题的回答
I hope we answer your three questions
能让你们满意
to your satisfaction.
达里尔  快走
Daryl, go!
把鲍勃弄出来
Let's get Bob.
再挪一点
More, more.
快  必须得走了
Come on, time to go.
走吧  快走  快
Let's go, now! Come on! Go!
扎克
Zack!
走吧  快走
Go, go!
就在前面了[双关]
It's just ahead.
埃迪
Eddie.
谢天谢地你还在这里
Oh, thank God you're still here.
他是瑞克
This is Rick.
他会帮助我们
He's gonna help us.
一切都会好的
Everything's gonna be okay.
一切
Everything--
可恶
Damn it!
我本来想把野猪带回来
I wanted to take the boar.
可我知道带你过来会更快
I just knew-- I knew I'd get you here so much quicker.
他饿坏了
He's starving.
他越来越蔫  他需要吃活物
He's slowing. He needs something alive.
求你  我说过  我不能没有他
Please, I told you, I can't be without him.
所以我才留着他
And so I kept him.
这是错的
It was wrong.
我不能做这种事
I can't do things like this.
但你必须这样做
And-- and you have to do things like this.
让我和他一样吧
Let me be like him.
不要阻拦
Don't stop it.
不要在这之后杀掉我们
Don't end it after.
-不  -让我同他在一起吧
- No. - Let me be with him.
不要
No!
你的...
What were...
问题是什么
the questions?
那三个问题
The three questions?
你杀过多少行尸
How many walkers have you killed?
埃迪
Eddie--
埃迪把它们都杀了
Eddie killed-- killed them all.
直到...
Until...
你杀过多少活人
How many people have you killed?
只有我自己
Just me.
为什么
Why?
你没法
You don't--
你没法回到过去
you don't get to come back.
有些事一旦发生  你就没法
You don't get to come back
回到过去
from things.
回不去...
You don't...
"孩子们盯着蜡烛
The children fastened their eyes upon their bit of candle
看着它缓缓地  无情地融化
and watched it melt slowly and pitilessly away.
最后只剩半寸孤独的灯芯
Saw the half inch of wick stand alone at last.
微弱的火苗忽上忽下
Saw the feeble flame rise and fall.
顺着轻烟而上
Climb the thin tower of smoke.
徘徊片刻  之后..."
Linger at its top a moment and then..."
女士  我该去放哨了吗
Ma'am, should I take watch now?
好的  卢克  去吧
Yes, Luke, you do that.
今天
Today...
我们来学习刀具的用法
We are talking about knives-- how to use them,
如何安全地使用  如何用它们救命
how to be safe with them, and how they could save your life.
女士  我能先走吗
Ma'am, may I be dismissed?
-怎么  -我不太舒服
- What is it? - I'm not feeling very well.
有时你要克服一下
Sometimes you're gonna have to fight through it.
万一你独自在外怎么办
What if you wind up out there alone?
因为不舒服就放弃自己吗
You just give up because you're feeling bad?
不  我只是不想吐在别人身上
No, it's just I don't want to yack on somebody.
去吧
Go.
好  今天我们学习如何握刀
Okay, today we're gonna learn how to hold a knife,
怎么砍刺  该瞄准哪里
how to stab and slash and where to aim for.
拜托  不要告诉你父亲
Please, don't tell your father.
怎么了
What?
我也不想去外面
I don't like going out there, either.
达里尔会告诉贝丝
Daryl's telling Beth.
这是没办法的事
There's nothing else to do.
我去找她
I'll go see her.
我没怀孕
I'm not pregnant.
-你知道了吗  -知道了
- You know? - I know.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我没打算要孩子  但我们可以要
I didn't want to, but we could have.
我们可以在这里生活
We can have lives here.
经历了洛莉和今天的事
How can you say that after today?
你怎能还这么说
After Lori?
因为我不想害怕活着
Because I don't want to be afraid of being alive.
会害怕才让我们活到了今天
Being afraid is what's kept us alive.
不是
No.
我们这只是苟延残喘
It's how we kept breathing.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hey.  -Hi.
怎么了
What is it?
扎克
Zack.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
噢
Okay.
30天无事故
怎么
What?
我再也不会哭了
I don't cry anymore, Daryl.
我只是觉得很高兴认识了他
I'm just glad I got to know him, you know?
我也是
Me, too.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
只是厌倦了同伴的离去
Just tired of losing people is all.
我很庆幸没有跟他道别
I'm glad I didn't say good-bye.
我讨厌道别
I hate good-byes.
我也是
Me, too.
梅肯
你试图帮她
You tried to help her.
你帮不了  没人帮得了
You couldn't. No one could.
有些人已经病入膏肓
Some people are too far gone.
而你没有
You're not.
你试图帮她
You tried to help her.
那个女人的状态
How that woman wound up,
我也差点成那样
I got close to that.
如果我失去了卡尔和朱迪思
If I lost Carl and Judith,
失去这个地方
if I lost this place--
不会的  瑞克  即使那样也不会
Not then, Rick. Not even then.
你回来了
You came back.
你的儿子回来了
Your boy came back.
你一定不会迷失
You get to come back. You do.
现代汽车为您带来《行尸走肉》下集预告
Hyundai presents this seaon on The Walking Dead...
退后
Come on back now!
我们必须维持这里运作
We have to keep this place going.
-瑞克  -快跑  离开这里
- Rick! - Go! Get out of here.
我们的人所剩无几了
There's not a lot of us left.
除非必要  不要开枪
You don't fire unless you absolutely need to.
我不能让你这么做
I can't let you do this.
别拦我
Don't stop me!
你为什么还在找总督
The Governor. Why you still looking for him?
要么开枪  要么跑
You shoot or you run.
左转
Go to the left.
卡住了
Jammed up.
更多视频请登录AMC官网查看
For more video go to amc.com.